Be careful!
It's after the Seals!
For a cornered beast with no way out, hardly a surprising choice
It seems that some losses are inevitable
As this constitutes "force majeure," I'm afraid the contract excuses me from providing compensation
Force majeure or not, I still have to try...
I must caution you, Miss Vesna
Borrowing too much power is a precarious move
I understand. Even so...
When that lady gave this power to my ancestors, perhaps the contract she made
Was for this purpose
That its custodian, when the time comes, should make a stand
"Contract"...
It's back up! How do we defeat this thing!?
Vesna, look out!
What the...
...Your Majesty?
...
I was hoping to sit this out...
But it seems I'll have to reclaim what is mine
Care to stop me
Your Majesty?
In all this time, I've had no great ambition to recover my stolen morsel
But if it were used to extract life, or even defy death...
It would be a grave transgression
Vesna, are you alright?
...What do you want?
People love to believe in the miraculous potential of human ingenuity...
And yet... Human effort is mostly futile